威尔 · 森坦斯: 303毫秒。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: At 303 milliseconds.
威尔 · 森塔斯(笑) : 我不知道为什么每个人都害怕这种期待。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: [LAUGH] I don't know
why everyone, fears this anticipation.
这是显而易见的。
It's obvious, surely.
我知道队列是怎么工作的，我甚至在队列之间放了一个逗号，所以
I know how queues work,
I even put a little comma between, so
我们真的知道排队是怎么回事。
we really know how queues work.
我的事件循环，在这里，让我们确保它在这里，在这里。
My event loop, there it is let's make
sure it's on there, there it is.
事件循环，就是检查这个是否为空的循环。
The event loop, that's the one that's
gonna do the checking if this is empty.
是空的吗？
Was it empty?
没有。
No.
全局上下文运行完毕了吗？
Was the global context finished running?
没有。
No.
所以事情没有进展，没有。
So the event was going nope, nope.
但是它变成了3毫秒。
But it turned to three milliseconds.
事件循环检查调用堆栈,
The event loop checks the call stack,
进一步检查，全局代码运行，然后它会说，我们可以走了吗？
checks it any further, global code to run,
and it goes, are we good to go?
我们可以走了，我们可以检查我们的队列了。
We're good to go,
we're good to check our queue.
什么，在那个时候，它会运行吗？
What, at that point, is it gonna run?
这应该很明显吧？
Well, it should be obvious?
谁愿意做志愿者？
Who would like to volunteer?
我不想要正确的答案,
I don't want the right answer,
我想知道排队所说的答案，就是这个答案。
I want the answer that follows what
a queue says is gonna be the answer here.
观众: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 布雷登,
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Brayden,
拜托，谢谢。
please, thank you.
布雷登: 火车，喂？
&gt;&gt; Brayden: Train hello?
威尔 · 桑塔斯: 当然，因为打印机[听不见]已经打印出来了
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Of course because
printers [INAUDIBLE] bcnf so
我知道排队是怎么回事,
long it's in the front of,
I know how a queue works and yet,
他从根本上来说是错的，我的意思是肯定是好的，而不是一些事情
he is fundamentally wrong I mean
surely nice rather some things and yet
这次不行[笑]观众: [笑]
not this time [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
威尔 · 森坦斯: 好吧,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: All right,
你觉得 Brayden 到底在跑什么？
what do you think runs actually Brayden?
布雷登: 展览。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: The display.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah.
但这没有道理，我知道队列是如何工作的。
But that makes no sense,
I know how queues work.
知识分子，有没有人可以放手一搏,
Can anybody take a leap
of faith intellectual,
这里可能会发生什么？
on what might be happening here instead?
这次由我来照顾凯拉。
I'm gonna tend to Kayla on this one.
排队的队伍不一样。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It's a different queue.
威尔 · 森特斯: 她说对了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: She got it right.
我告诉你，在我做这个演讲的所有时间里，我会说一个或者
I tell you, in all the time I've
given this talk, I would say one or
有两倍的人会这么做。
two times that people
would take that leap.
凭直觉的信念，对凯拉大声疾呼，完全正确。
Of intuit faith, so
huge shout out to Kayla, exactly right.
还有一个额外的队列。
There's an additional queue.
别误会,
Now don't get me wrong,
我留下的这个大空间可能是个线索。
this big space here that I left might
have been something of a giveaway.
观众: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 但是那真是太棒了,
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But that is fantastic,
谢谢 Kayla。
thank you to Kayla.
完全正确，事实上还有另一个队列。
Exactly right,
there is in fact another queue.
在规范中，他们称之为任务队列。
It's called, they call this in the spec,
the task queue.
所以，你可以猜猜另一个叫什么。
So, you can maybe take a guess
what the other one is called.
它被称为微任务队列。
It's called the microtask queue.
这就是微任务队列。
There it is, the microtask queue.
当显示被触发时，我们会在哪里思考
And where do we think when
display is triggered, and
准备好跑了吗，我们认为显示器会出现吗？
ready to run,
do we think display shows up?
凯拉是在回复队列还是微任务队列？
Kayla is it in the callback queue,
or the microtask queue?
微任务队列。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: The microtask queue.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 微任务队列，她正好进入微任务队列。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The microtask queue,
she is spot on into the microtask queue.
顺便说一句,
It went display, with by the way,
准备插入的高论点,
the high argument ready
to be inserted into it,
高达270毫秒的数据。
the high data at 270 milliseconds.
在那里，让我们把它从队列的后面拿出来。
There it is, let's get it out
of the back of the queue here.
不不不不。
No, no, no, no, no.
不在这里，感谢布雷登的配合。
Not here, thank you to Brayden for
playing along.
不，不在队伍的后面，那么，在哪里呢？
No, not at the back of the queue there,
and so, where?
一旦303毫秒的事件循环消失,
Once the event loop at
303 milliseconds goes,
我们清楚同步全球代码了。
we're clear on
the synchronous global code.
Kayla 你觉得会不会是第一个,
Where Kayla,
do you think it heads to first,
你觉得它会先排到哪个队？
which queue do you think
it heads to first?
微任务队列 Will Sentance: 微任务队列
&gt;&gt; Kayla: The microtask queue
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The microtask queue
她的位置，它抓取显示，它排队，抓取它的代码。
she's spot on, it grabs display
it dequeues it, grabs its code.
它把它放在调用堆栈上。
It puts it on the call stack.
通过自动插入参数,
With the inserted argument automatically,
的值高，它添加了父母自动 JavaScript。
of the value high, it adds
the parental automatically JavaScript.
它会自动插入参数 JavaScript。
It inserts the argument
JavaScript automatically.
我喜欢。
I love that.
所以这点非常重要。
So that's very important to sort of spot.
然后它执行它，然后，对马特来说。
And it executes it, and so what, to Matt.
马特，在303毫秒的时候，我们的控制台会显示什么？
Matt, what's gonna show up in our console,
at 303 milliseconds?
马特: 高 威尔 · 森特斯: 会很高,
&gt;&gt; Matt: High.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's gonna be high,
我应该问托德的。
I should have asked Todd.
会很高精确到303毫秒,
It's gonna be high,
exactly at 303 milliseconds,
我们在我们的控制台里很兴奋。
we get high in our console.
最后，我们可怜的小,
And finally, our poor little,
微任务队列现在是空的。
the microtask queue is now empty.
事件循环终于结束了。
And the event loop finally goes.
是时候进入回调队列了。
It's time to go down
to the callback queue.
它在哪里找到了什么？
Where what does it find?
但是我们的小朋友打印你好,
But our little friend print hello,
已经等了304毫秒了。
who's been waiting there for
304 milliseconds.
但是，从调用堆栈中删除显示之后，它运行完毕,
But, after removing display from
the call stack, it's finished running,
我们终于到了304毫秒
we're finally at 304 milliseconds,
are able for
事件循环检查最后的队列，回调队列。
the event loop to check our final queue,
the callback queue.
其中304毫秒，print hello 已经坐在那里准备运行。
Where for 304 milliseconds, print hello
has been sitting there ready to run.
这是梦想，但现在是它的时刻。
It's dreamed, but now is its moment.
看看它有多自豪。
Look how proud it is.
它跳起来，进入调用堆栈。
It jumps up, into the call stack.
在那里，它在调用堆栈上以304毫秒的速度打印 hello。
There it is print hello on the call
stack at 304 milliseconds.
那么在304毫秒时，我们在控制台中看到了什么呢？
What therefore Ethan at 304 milliseconds,
what do we see in our console then?
什么是控制台日志，但是？
What's gonna console log but?
伊森: 你好。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Hello.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 你好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Hello.
没错。
Exactly.
[声音]哇，伙计们，干得好。
[SOUND] Wow people, well done.
天哪，这就是幕后的同步 JavaScript 的整个模型。
My goodness, that is the entire model of a
synchronous JavaScript behind the scenes.
我们有两个队列。
We have two queues.
我们将 print hello 加入队列，然后从调用堆栈中取出它。
We enqueue print hello, we pop it
off the call stack at that point.
我们有两个队列，任何从 JavaScript 中抛出的函数,
We have two queues, any function
that is thrown out of JavaScript,
或者至少一个链接会从 JavaScript 中删除,
or at least a link back to it
is thrown out of JavaScript,
通过传统的回调 facade 函数，比如 set timeout。
via the old school callback facade
functions like set timeout.
这些函数在后台工作完成后，位于回调队列的第二位。
Those functions when the background work
is complete, second in the callback queue.
任何通过 then 方法附加到承诺对象的函数,
Any function that is attached to
a promise object via the then method,
然后自动触发运行 JavaScript
and then auto triggered to
run from within JavaScript
当 promise 对象的 value 属性自动更新时,
when the value property that promise
object gets updated automatically,
作为背景工作的结果，从双管齐下的立面功能，如获取。
as a result of the background work from
a two pronged facade function like fetch.
这个函数不会进入回调队列。
That function ain't going
in the callback queue.
它进入了微任务队列。
It's going in the microtask queue.
当所有全局代码运行完毕时,
And when all global code
is finished running, and
调用栈上什么都没有，事件循环检查队列。
there's nothing on the call stack,
the event loop goes and checks the queues.
它先检查哪一个？
Which does it check first?
微任务队列。
The microtask queue.
它去除函数的队列，运行它，并且
It dequeues the function, runs it, and
直到最后它才检查回调队列。
then only finally then does
it check the callback queue.